Guide to the Rice University Past Faculty and Staff records, 1961-1996 UA 008
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Past Faculty and Staff A-Z, 1949-1992, 119387
  - Vardy, Katherine - Spanish, 1986; 170343 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Vaughn, Caryn Carpenter - Geology and Geophysics, 1986; 170344 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Von Bruch, Michael - Religious Studies, 1988; 170345 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Von Lutz, Bruno - English, 1988; 170346 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Vorhaben, Jean E. - Biology, 1984-1987; 170347 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Waigant, C. Alexander - Health and Physical Education, 1984-1988; 170348 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Walker, Mary Elizabeth - Economics, 1985; 170349 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Wallace, Fred - Economics, 1982-1983; 170350 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Walp, Robert - Shepherd School of Music, 1983-1988; 170351 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Walsh, Harry H. - German and Russiabn, 1984-1985; 170352 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Warren, Paul R. - Philosophy, 1986-1988; 170353 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Watkins, Joel S. - Geology and Geophysics, 1987-1988; 170354 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Webbink, Elizabeth S. - Administrative Science, 1987; 170355 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Wehrung, Donald A. - Administration, 1986; 170356 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Westergaard, Kimberly A. - Health and Physical Education, 1985; 170357 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - White, Luise Susan - History, 1983-1986; 170358 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Williams-Manigault, Bisa - English, 1981-1984; 170359 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Wilson, Timothy R. - Health and Physical Education, 1985-1987; 170360 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Wise, Scott - Accounting, 1981-1988; 170361 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Wolf, Gabriel - Electrican and Computer Engineering, 1985-1986; 170362 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Wolfson, Jon Gordon - Mathematics, 1982-1985; 170363 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Woods, Daniel J. - Mathematical Sciences, 1986; 170364 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Yamal, Gloria J. - Spanish, 1987; 170365 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - You, Jia-Huai - Computer Science, 1985-1986; 170366 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Young, Colin - Art and Art History, 1986; 170367 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Zander, Benjamin - Shepherd School of Music, 1985-1986; 170368 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Zheng, Yunbo - Mathematics, 1987-1988; 170369 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Series VI: Past Faculty and Staff A-Z, 1953-1993, 166925
  - Abbatangelo, Rocco - Administrative Science, 1991-1992; 170370 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Abbott, Lee K. - English, 1987-1988; 170371 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Addison, Anthony - Shepherd School of Music, 1984-1992; 170372 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Albert, Mitchell A. - Administrative Science, 1990-1991; 170373 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Alspaugh, R. Blanton - Shepherd School of Music, 1986-1987; 170374 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Ames, Karen A. - Mathematical Sciences, 1989-1990; 170375 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Arad, Atar - Shepherd School of Music, 1987-1991; 170376 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Armstrong, Sarah - Biochemistry and Cell Biology, 1990; 170377 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Austin, Walter J. - Civil Engineering, 1960-1990; 170378 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Bacon, Thomas C. - Shepherd School of Music, 1985-1991; 170379 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Barnes, Mary W. - Art and Art History, 1983-1989; 170380 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Barrett, Deborah - Communications, 1989-1993; 170381 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Baum, Ernest R. - Education, 1962-1988; 170382 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Bay, Paul N. - Civil Engineering, 1988-1990; 170383 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Beckman, Herbert W. K. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1957-1990; 170384 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Bell, Philip W. - Administrative Science, 1977-1989; 170385 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Ben-Dor, Gisele - Shepherd School of Music, 1989-1990; 170386 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Bergmann, Rachelle - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1986, 1989; 170387 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Bible, Frances - Shepherd School of Music, 1976-1991; 170388 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Bilger, David E. - Shepherd School of Music, 1988-1991; 170389 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Birringer, Johannes - Humanities, 1989-1990; 170390 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Blumberg, Mitchell - Administrative Science, 1981-1991; 170391 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Boehm, Han-Juergen K. H. - Computer Science, 1984-1989; 170392 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Bougen, Philip D. - Accounting, 1988-1990; 170393 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Bourjea, Serge - French and Italian, 1989; 170394 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Bowen, Ray M. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1990; 170395 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Brancart, Evelyne - Shepherd School of Music, 1990-1991; 170396 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Bray, Molly S. - Human Performance and Health Sciences, 1994-1995; 170397 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Briggs, Faye A. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1982-1991; 170398 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Brooks, Kerry - Administrative Science, 1988-1989; 170399 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Bross, Helmut - Physics/Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1988-1989; 170400 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Brown, Barry W. - Statistics/Mathematical Sciences, 1970-1993; 170401 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Brown, Katherine - Art and Art History, 1963-1989; 170402 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Brown, Larry - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1993; 170403 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Burch, Robert W. - Philosophy, 1992; 170404 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Burguete, Esteban - Mathematical Sciences, 1990; 170405 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Caballero, William - Shepherd School of Music, 1985-1990; 170406 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Caldwell, Robert H. - Marine Officer Instructor/Naval Science, 1990-[?]; 170407 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Callahan, David - Computer Science, 1988-1993; 170408 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Campbell, Cheney - Accounting, 1991-1992; 170409 (Box 19, Folder 70)
  - Carter, Andre Lewis - Naval Science, 1992-[?]; 170410 (Box 19, Folder 71)
  - Casperson, Paul - Economics, 1990; 170411 (Box 19, Folder 72)
  - Chaisson, William - Shepherd School of Music, 1983-1991; 170412 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Chang, Donald Choy - Biophysics, 1974-1992; 170413 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Chen, Chuanchang - English, 1988-1990; 170414 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Chen, Guanrong - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1988-1990; 170415 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Chen, Ziangkun - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1988-1991; 170416 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Chiu, Shean-Tsong - Statistics, 1984-1989; 170417 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Choe, Jaigyoung - Mathematics, 1988-1989; 170418 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Claborn, F. Jay - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1990; 170419 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Cockshutt, Timothy - Administrative Science, 1990-1991; 170420 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Cohen, Robert J. - English, 1989; 170421 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Colson, David - Shepherd School of Music, 1988-1989; 170422 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Constant, Caroline - Architecture, 1989; 170423 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Cook, Robert - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1990-1991; 170424 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Cooper, Paul - Shepherd School of Music, 1974-1996; 170425 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Cunningham, George R. - Architecture, 1981-1990; 170426 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Curtis, Doris M. - Geology and Geophysics, 1979-1992; 170427 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Davezac, Bertrand - Art and Art History/Curator, 1979-1992; 170428 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - David, Alan - English, 1989; 170429 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Day, Amelia Rebecca - Education, 1988; 170430 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - DeVille, Chris Moore - Education, 1989; 170431 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - de Vries, Nick - Art and Art History, 1991; 170432 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Drew, Patrick D. - Accounting, 1990; 170433 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Dunlap, William J. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1981-1992; 170434 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Eaker, Helen E. - Classics, 1965-1993; 170435 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Ellis, Grover - Administrative Science, 1986-1990; 170436 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Erickson, Jon David - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1988-1990; 170437 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Farrell, Michele L. - French, 1984-1988; 170438 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Finer, Judith - Administrative Science, 1988-1991; 170439 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Fong, Steven T. - Architecture, 1989; 170440 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Freeman, Thomas F. - Religious Studies, 1972-1992; 170441 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Friederick, Patricia E. - French and Italian, 1988-1989; 170442 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Friedman, Tom - Administrative Science, 1991-1992; 170443 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Friend, Harlan J. - Human Performance and Health Sciences, 1988-1989; 170444 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Galicki, Krzysztof - Mathematics, 1987-1990; 170445 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Gallop, Jane - Humanities/French/Italian, 1985-1990; 170446 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Garcia, Charles A. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1973-1991; 170447 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Garrity, Thomas A. - Mathematics, 1986-1989; 170448 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Getz, J. Greg - Sociology, 1989; 170449 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Ghanem, Roger G. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1989-1990; 170450 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Gillan, Douglas J. - Psychology, 1988-1990; 170451 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Glacken, Michael W. - Chemical Engineering, 1987-1990; 170452 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Goad, Candice S. - Philosophy, 1992; 170453 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Golb, Joel David - German and Slavic Studies, 1988-1991; 170454 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Goldman, Jane - Art and Art History, 1989-1990; 170455 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Griffin, Campbell - Administrative Science, 1992; 170456 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Griffin, Timothy George - Computer Science, 1990; 170457 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Grotowski, Joseph F. - Mathematics, 1990-1991; 170458 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Hall, David - Head Baseball Coach, 1981-1991; 170459 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Hall, Elizabeth R. - Biomedical Engineering Laboratory, 1984-1991; 170460 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Hallam, John S. - Art and Art History, 1981-1989; 170461 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Harlan, William E. - Administrative Science, 1990-1992; 170462 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Harris, Richard, III - Computer Science, 1989-1992; 170463 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Harrison, Karey Lea - Philosophy, 1987-1989; 170464 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Hassett, Jim - Accounting, 1987-1991; 170465 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Hatchett, Terry E. - Accounting, 1982-1991; 170466 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Heckelman, Ronald J. - English, 1988-1991; 170467 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Hegarty, Kerry A. - Geology and Geophysics, 1992-1993; 170468 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Hendrix, Mark D. - Accounting, 1989; 170469 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Heronemus, Ellen Hill - Education, 1988-1990; 170470 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Hershey, Olive - English, 1988; 170471 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Hill, Albina N. S. - German and Slavic Studies, 1983-1985; 170472 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Hill, Robert - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1991-1993; 170473 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Hillar, Janett - Spanish, 1989; 170474 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Hofto, Jacqueline - Shepherd School of Music, 1989-1990; 170475 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Holstrom, Lasse - Statistics, 1993; 170476 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Hood, Robert Todd - Computer Science, 1981-1988 [?]; 170477 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Hook, Jay Gravett - Psychology, 1989; 170478 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Hughes, Colin R. - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1989; 170479 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Hull, David - Administrative Science, 1990-1991; 170481 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Inscoe, John - History, 1988-1989; 170482 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Isgur, Marvin - Administrative Science, 1983-1990; 170483 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Jackson, Roy - Chemical Engineering, 1989-1990; 170484 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Johnson, Olin G. - Geology and Geophysics, 1988-1989; 170485 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Johnson, Paul M. - Political Science, 1988-1989; 170486 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Johnston, Dennis A. - Statistics, 1979-1992; 170487 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Jones, Charlotte Harrison - Accounting, 1990-1991; 170488 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Jones, Edward D. B. - Architecture (offer not accepted), 1989; 170489 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Jones, Elizabeth A. - Communications, 1990-1993; 170490 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Jones, Wesley - Architecture, 1989; 170491 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Jost, Robert J. - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1980-1989; 170492 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Jun, Byoung Heon - Economics, 1988-1989; 170493 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Kahan, Alan - History, 1988-1992; 170494 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Kahn, Kathryn - Art and Art History, 1991; 170495 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Kaspar, E. H. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1990-1992; 170496 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Kauffman, Thomas B. - Statistics, 1988-1989; 170497 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Keeley, Jack W. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1981-1992; 170498 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Kehoe, John Kimball - Administrative Science, 1988-1993; 170499 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Kellogg, Susan M. - Anthropology, 1988-1989; 170500 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Kiepper, Alan - Public Administration, 1982-1990; 170501 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Klinghardt, Matthias - Religious Studies, 1988-1989; 170502 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Knox, Robert G. - Biology, 1987-1990; 170503 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Kolenda, Konstantin - Philosophy, 1953-1992; 170504 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Kolenda, Pauline - Anthropology, 1988-1989; 170505 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Konrad, Gyorgy - History (offer not accepted), 1990; 170506 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Kotarba, Joseph A. - Sociology, 1990; 170507 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Kroger, Harry - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1987-1990; 170508 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Kumura, Mineo - Physics, 1988-1992; 170509 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Ladenson, Elisabeth - French and Italian, 1990; 170510 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - LaViolette, Adria - Anthropology, 1989-1990; 170511 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Lawton, Wayne M. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1988-1990; 170512 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - LeCompte, Margaret D. - Anthropology, 1988-1989; 170513 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Leffel, Anita - Director of MBA/MAcco Student Affairs/Communications, 1988-1990; 170514 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Levin, Donald Norman - Classics, 1963-1992; 170515 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Lewis, Robert M. - Mathematical Sciences, 1990; 170516 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Lichtenstein, Therese - Art and Art History, 1992; 170517 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Linder, Mark - Architecture, 1991; 170518 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Loewenheim, Francis L. - History, 1959-1996; 170519 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Logan, Marie-Rose - French and Italian (1 of 2), 1983-1988; 170520 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Logan, Marie-Rose - French and Italian (2 of 2), 1983-1988; 170521 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Lott, John R., Jr. - Economics, 1987-1989; 170522 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Loukissas, Philippos J. - Administrative Science, 1987-1990; 170523 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Lukitsh, Joanne Mary - Art and Art History, 1987-1989; 170524 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Luxemburg, Leon A. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1988-1989; 170525 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Macken, Marlys - Anthropology, 1990-1991; 170526 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Magalis, Richard L. - Naval Science, 1989-[?]; 170527 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Mancini, Matthew J. - History, 1990-1991; 170528 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Marowsky, Gerd H. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1980-1991; 170529 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Martin, Joseph P. - Biology, 1981-1988; 170530 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Martinez, Hector J. - Mathematical Sciences, 1989; 170531 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Mayer, Uri - Shepherd School of Music, 1986-1989; 170532 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - McCarthy, Matthew - Mathematical Sciences, 1990; 170533 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - McCormick, Patricia B. - Administrative Science, 1989; 170534 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - McCoy, Robert A. - Art and Art History, 1988-1989; 170535 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Melendez, Gabriel - Mathematical Sciences, 1987-1989; 170536 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Middleton, David - Mathematical Sciences, 1979-1989; 170537 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Mikhail, Osama I. - Administrative Science, 1988-1990; 170538 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Mitchell, O. Jack - Architecture, 1966-1991; 170539 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Mixon, John - Architecture, 1969-1991; 170540 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Montgomery, Joseph C. - Psychology, 1988-1990; 170541 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Morrison, Lucian L., Jr. - Administrative Science, 1988-1990; 170542 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Moseley, S. Kelley - Administration, 1987-1988; 170543 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Moss, Ned C. - Co-Director of the Rice Summer School/Education, 1988-1990; 170544 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Murphy, Paul H. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1980-1991; 170545 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Murray, Fred F. - Administrative Science, 1988-1993; 170546 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Murray, Russell - Shepherd School of Music, 1990-1991; 170547 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Nagata, Fumiko - Japanese, 1988-1989; 170548 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Nelson, John Robert - Religious Studies, 1988-1991; 170549 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Newfield, Christopher - English, 1987-1989; 170550 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Nickols, Thomas D. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1989; 170551 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Noble, Stephen T. - Space Physics and Astronomy, 1986-1993; 170552 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Nogee, Joseph L. - Political Science, 1990; 170553 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Norton, John D. - English, 1988-1989; 170554 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Nudelman, Harvey B. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1982-1991; 170555 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Ostendorg, David W. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1988-1989; 170556 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Papademetriou, Peter C. - Architecture, 1968-1990; 170557 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Papamichalis, Panagiotis E. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1987-1991; 170561 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Papoutsakis, Eleftherios Terry - Chemical Engineering, 1979-1991; 170562 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Parks, Thomas W. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1967-1990; 170563 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Parslow, Christopher - Art and Art History, 1989-1990; 170564 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Pears, David - Philosophy, 1991; 170565 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Pegg, Ian L. - Chemical Engineering (offer withdrawn), 1987; 170566 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Perin, Constance - Anthropology, 1990; 170567 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Peters, Albert W. - Human Performance and Health Sciences, 1983-1993; 170568 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Philippe, Edouard - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1982-1992; 170569 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Pickar, Richard W. - Shepherd School of Music, 1976-1991; 170570 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Planell, Rafael Martinez - Mathematical Sciences, 1990-1991; 170571 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Polakoff, Michael A. - Adminstrative Science, 1987-1990; 170572 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Pollock, Lori L. - Computer Science, 1986-1990; 170573 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Porter, Carolyn - English, 1990; 170574 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Posth, Matthew - Philosophy, 1989-1990; 170575 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Pritchard, Robert E. - Mechanical Engineering, 1987-1991; 170576 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Raaphorst, Madeleine R. - French, 1963-1989; 170577 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Raulston, Dwight L. - Computer Science, 1985-1989; 170578 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Rhoades, Howard M. - Psychology, 1989; 170579 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Rice, Martin A., Jr. - Philosophy, 1988-1990; 170580 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Rose, Beatrice S. - Shepherd School of Music, 1987-1993; 170581 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Ross, Marty - Mathematics, 1989-1992; 170582 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Rowe, Colin F. - Architecture, 1989-1990; 170583 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Rudisill, Marianne - Psychology, 1989-1990; 170584 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Ryan, Jeffrey J. - Political Science, 1989-1991; 170585 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Sabalos, James C. - Administrative Science, 1987-1991; 170586 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Sachs, Ekkebard Wolfgang - Materials Science, 1988-1989; 170587 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Sachs, Michael - Shepherd School of Music, 1987-1988; 170588 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Savino, Charles R. - Administrative Science, 1988-1989; 170589 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Scardaville, Thomas C. - Administrative Science, 1988-1990; 170590 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Schaezler, Donald J. - Environmental Science and Engineering, 1979-1993; 170591 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Schrader, Cheryl - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1991-1992; 170592 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Schlesinger, John - Art and Art History, 1988-1989; 170593 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Schreiber, Janet M. - Anthropology, 1975-1992; 170594 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Schroder, Gene D. - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology, 1978-1992; 170595 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Semczuk, Antoni - German and Slavic Studies, 1989; 170596 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Seriff, Aaron J. - Geology and Geophysics, 1982-1992; 170597 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Seymour, Lynne M. - Humanities, 1990-1992; 170598 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Shetty, Anand B. - Human Performance and Health Sciences, 1987-1990; 170599 (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Sigrist, Markus R. - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1990; 170600 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Skaggs, Ray H. - Human Performance and Health Sciences, 1972-1993; 170601 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Slayton, Barney F. - Military Science, 1987-1988; 170602 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Smith, Alexander - Mathematics, 1987-1990; 170603 (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Smith, Elizabeth A. - Administration, 1989; 170604 (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Solis, R. Thomas - Biomedical Engineering, 1980-1989; 170605 (Box 22, Folder 55)
  - Solomon, Barbara S. - Architecture, 1989; 170606 (Box 22, Folder 56)
  - Soltero, Luis - Computer Science, 1986-1992; 170607 (Box 22, Folder 57)
  - Sonntag, Christopher - Naval Science, 1987-[?]; 170608 (Box 22, Folder 58)
  - Spears, Larry G. - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1989; 170609 (Box 22, Folder 59)
  - Sperling, Harry G. - Biology, 1982-1990; 170610 (Box 22, Folder 60)
  - Streng, William P. - Political Science, 1986-1989; 170611 (Box 22, Folder 61)
  - Suitts, Thomas B. - Head Basketball Coach, 1981-1987; 170612 (Box 22, Folder 62)
  - Su, Wu-Pei - Mechanical Engineering and Materials Science, 1989; 170613 (Box 22, Folder 63)
  - Sullivan, Stephen - Philosophy, 1988-1989; 170614 (Box 22, Folder 64)
  - Swearingen, Daniel - Mathematics, 1989-1992; 170615 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Taner, M. Turhan - Geology and Geophysics, 1988-1993; 170616 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Tarrazaga, Pablo - Mathematical Sciences, 1990; 170617 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Todd, Anderson - Architecture, 1949-1992; 170618 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Todorova, Maria - History, 1990-1991; 170619 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Trueman, Mary - Shepherd School of Music, 1990 [?]-1993; 170620 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Tuggle, Francis D. - Administrative Science, 1978-1989; 170621 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Ulrich, Roger B. - Art and Art History, 1984-1989; 170622 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Vu, Phuong - Mathematical Sciences, 1989-1993; 170623 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Wall, Scott W. - Architecture, 1988-1989; 170624 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Waters, C. Kenneth - Philosophy, 1987-1990; 170625 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Waters, David L. - Shepherd School of Music, 1976-1993; 170626 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Weiher, Gregory R. - Political Science, 1989-1990; 170627 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Weiland, Siep - Electrical and Computer Engineering, 1991; 170628 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Weiser, Alan - Mathematical Sciences, 1990-1991; 170629 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Wetzel, William Fred - Psychology, 1989; 170630 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - White, Frank S. - Architecture, 1982-1993; 170631 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - White, Robert A. - Statistics, 1981-1993; 170632 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Wicks, Camilla - Shepherd School of Music, 1987-1991; 170633 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Wilford, Michael - Architecture, 1979-1989; 170634 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Willbern, David - English, 1989; 170635 (Box 23, Folder 19)